Register of the Commonwealth Club of California records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Program File, 1916-2006 (Boxes 382-605)
  - 1988
    - Sheehy, Gail (Box-folder 521: 22)
    - Shorenstein, Walter H. (Box-folder 521: 23)
    - Stone, Oliver (Box-folder 521: 24)
    - Theroux, Paul Edward (Box-folder 521: 25)
    - Thomas, Debi (Box-folder 521: 26)
    - Tolchin, Martin and Susan (Box-folder 521: 27)
    - Tonegawa, Susumu (Box-folder 521: 28)
    - Van Walt, Michael (Box-folder 521: 29)
    - Wenner, Jann S. (Box-folder 521: 30)
    - Wiesel, Elie (Box-folder 521: 31)
    - Williams, Robin (Box-folder 521: 32)
    - Yuetter, Clayton K. (Box-folder 521: 33)
  - 1989
    - Abelson, Alan (Box-folder 521: 34)
    - Abourezk, James (Box-folder 521: 35)
    - American/Korean panel of speakers (Box-folder 521: 36)
    - Arledge, Roone (Box-folder 521: 37)
    - Atwater, Lee (Box-folder 521: 38)
    - Avanzino, Richard (Box-folder 521: 39)
    - Ballard, Robert (Box-folder 521: 40)
    - Barnes, Fred (Box-folder 521: 41)
    - Bartolo, Eddie de (Box-folder 521: 42)
    - Bettelheim, Bruno (Box-folder 521: 43)
    - Bierbauer, Charles (Box-folder 522: 1)
    - Cárdenas Solórzano, Cuauhtémoc (Box-folder 522: 2)
    - Chace, William M. (Box-folder 522: 3)
    - Cheney, Richard B. (Box-folder 522: 4)
    - Chimerine, Lawrence (Box-folder 522: 5)
    - Cohen, Marcia (Box-folder 522: 6)
    - Cowper, Steve (Box-folder 522: 7)
    - Crane, Edward H. (Box-folder 522: 8)
    - Crocker, Chester A. (Box-folder 522: 9)
    - Dalai Lama (Box-folder 522: 10)
    - Dehennin, Herman (Box-folder 522: 11)
    - Delors, Jacques (Box-folder 522: 12)
    - Derwinski, Edward J. (Box-folder 522: 13)
    - Eisenhower, David (Box-folder 522: 14)
    - Ellemann-Jensen, Uffe (Box-folder 522: 15)
    - Elorabi, Nabil (Box-folder 522: 16)
    - Escalante, Jaime (Box-folder 522: 17)
    - Fairbanks, Douglas (Box-folder 522: 18)
    - Forbes, Steve (Box-folder 522: 19)
    - Foss, Joseph (Box-folder 522: 20)
    - Futrele, Mary Hatwood (Box-folder 522: 21)
    - Galbraith, Evan (Box-folder 522: 22)
    - Gallup, George (Box-folder 522: 23)
    - Gassée, Jean-Louis (Box-folder 522: 24)
    - Gerol, Ilya (Box-folder 522: 25)
    - Gharekhan, C. R. (Box-folder 522: 26)
    - Gomes, Steve (Box-folder 522: 27)
    - Goodall, Jane (Box-folder 522: 28)
    - Goodman, Ellen (Box-folder 522: 29)
    - Gray, William H. (Box-folder 522: 30)
    - Grodin, Joseph R. (Box-folder 522: 31)
    - Haas, Robert D. (Box-folder 522: 32)
    - Haley, P. Edward (Box-folder 523: 1)
    - Handley, Margie (Box-folder 523: 2)
    - Hardy, Dorcas R. (Box-folder 523: 3)
    - Harte, John (Box-folder 523: 4)
    - Harvey, Paul (Box-folder 523: 5)
    - Hector, Gary (Box-folder 523: 6)
    - Hegarty, Christopher J. (Box-folder 523: 7)
    - Held, Richard W. (Box-folder 523: 8)
    - Hobson, Alan (Box-folder 523: 9)
    - Hoffman, Dustin (Box-folder 523: 10)
    - Horne, Lena (Box-folder 523: 11)
    - Howe, Geoffrey (Box-folder 523: 12)
    - Hyde, Henry J. (Box-folder 523: 13)
    - Inman, Bobby R. (Box-folder 523: 14)
    - Irving, John (Box-folder 523: 15)
    - Jazairg, Idriss (Box-folder 523: 16)
    - Jennings, Peter (Box-folder 523: 17)
    - Johnson, John H. (Box-folder 523: 18)
    - Johnston, Moira (Box-folder 523: 19)
    - Jones, Cleve (Box-folder 523: 20)
    - Joseph, Fred (Box-folder 523: 21)
    - Kael, Pauline (Box-folder 523: 22)
    - Kafity, Samir (Box-folder 523: 23)
    - Kaufman, Henry (Box-folder 523: 24)
    - Kauzlarich, Richard Dale (Box-folder 523: 25)
    - Keillor, Garrison (Box-folder 523: 26)
    - Keller, George M. (Box-folder 524: 1)
    - Kelley, James C. (Box-folder 524: 2)
    - Kiep, Walter Leisler (Box-folder 524: 3)
    - Kiplinger, Austin H. (Box-folder 524: 4)
    - Knight, Bobby (Box-folder 524: 5)
    - Kondracke, Morton (Box-folder 524: 6)
    - Korbut, Olga (Box-folder 524: 7)
    - Lamm, Richard (Box-folder 524: 8)
    - Lane, Laurena William (Box-folder 524: 9)
    - Lapidus, Gail (Box-folder 524: 10)
    - Lawn, John (Box-folder 524: 11)
    - Lear, Frances (Box-folder 524: 12)
    - Lee, Eugene (Box-folder 524: 13)
    - Lee, George (Box-folder 524: 14)
    - Linkletter, Art (Box-folder 524: 15)
    - McCosker, John E. (Box-folder 524: 16)
    - McCurdy, Dave (Box-folder 524: 17)
    - Macklin, Gordon (Box-folder 524: 18)
    - McNamara, Robert S. (Box-folder 524: 19)
    - Mansfield, Michael J. (Box-folder 524: 20)
    - Mansouri, Lofti (Box-folder 524: 21)
    - Matlock, Jack F. (Box-folder 524: 22)
    - Mecca, Andrew M. (Box-folder 524: 23)
    - Mikhail-Ashrawi, Hanan (Box-folder 524: 24)
    - Milosz, Czeslaw (Box-folder 525: 1)
    - Mitchell, George (Box-folder 525: 2)
    - Mubarak, Hosni (Box-folder 525: 3)
    - Nabti, Michel (Box-folder 525: 4)
    - Nam, Duck-Woo (Box-folder 525: 5)
    - Neuharth, Allen (Box-folder 525: 6)
    - New business opportunities in Hungary (Box-folder 525: 7)
    - Newman, Paul (Box-folder 525: 8)
    - Noonan, John (Box-folder 525: 9)
    - Nunes, Marianna (Box-folder 525: 10)
    - O'Connor, John (Box-folder 525: 11)
    - Osterbrock, Donald (Box-folder 525: 12)
    - Packard, David (Box-folder 525: 13)
    - Packard, George R. (Box-folder 525: 14)
    - Palmer, Arnold (Box-folder 525: 15)
    - Parker, Donn B. (Box-folder 525: 16)
    - Patel, Kumar N. (Box-folder 525: 17)
    - Peace Corps (Box-folder 525: 18)
    - Penzias, Arno A. (Box-folder 525: 19)
    - Phillips, Warren (Box-folder 525: 20)
    - Plotkin, Mark (Box-folder 525: 21)
    - Polsby, Nelson (Box-folder 525: 22)
    - Powell, Colin L. (Box-folder 525: 23)
    - Raven, Robert (Box-folder 525: 24)
    - Riding, Alan (Box-folder 525: 25)
    - Riney, Hal (Box-folder 525: 26)
    - Roberts, George (Box-folder 525: 27)
    - Rockefeller, David (Box-folder 525: 28)
    - Romney, George (Box-folder 525: 29)
    - Rosen, Marty (Box-folder 525: 30)
    - Rosenfeld, Arthur H. (Box-folder 525: 31)
    - Rozelle, Pete (Box-folder 525: 32)
    - Ruder, David S. (Box-folder 526: 1)
    - Russian delegation (Box-folder 526: 2)
    - Sandler, Marion (Box-folder 526: 3)
    - Satre, Philip G. (Box-folder 526: 4)
    - Schell, Orville (Box-folder 526: 5)
    - Schirra, Walter M. (Box-folder 526: 6)
    - Schlesinger, Arthur (Box-folder 526: 7)
    - Schmidt, Rudi (Box-folder 526: 8)
    - Schreyer, William A. (Box-folder 526: 9)
    - Schwartz, Felice N. (Box-folder 526: 10)
    - Scott, Ildiko (Box-folder 526: 11)
    - Scowcroft, Brent (Box-folder 526: 12)
    - Serebrjakov, Alexander V. (Box-folder 526: 13)
    - Sheehan, Neil (Box-folder 526: 14)
    - Silas, G. J. (Box-folder 526: 15)
    - Singhji, Gaj (Box-folder 526: 16)
    - Skinner, Samuel K. (Box-folder 526: 17)
    - Smith, Joshua (Box-folder 526: 18)
    - Sowell, Thomas (Box-folder 526: 19)
    - Stephen, Ninian (Box-folder 526: 20)
    - Sullivan, Mike (Box-folder 526: 21)
    - Susman, Frank (Box-folder 526: 22)
    - Thompson, John (Box-folder 526: 23)
    - Toffler, Alvin (Box-folder 526: 24)
    - Trade with USSR (Box-folder 526: 25)
    - Trudeau, Garry B. (Box-folder 526: 26)
    - Tupper, John (Box-folder 526: 27)
    - Tylor, Ann (Box-folder 526: 28)
    - Ueberroth, Peter (Box-folder 526: 29)
    - USA-USSR dialogue (Box-folder 526: 30)
    - Van de Kamp, John (Box-folder 526: 31)
    - Villanueva, Roberto (Box-folder 526: 32)
    - Viller, Arturo (Box-folder 527: 1)
    - Walker, Alice (Box-folder 527: 2)
    - Wall, M. Danny (Box-folder 527: 3)
    - Wallerstein, Judith S. (Box-folder 527: 4)
    - Webster, William H. (Box-folder 527: 5)
    - Will, George (Box-folder 527: 6)
    - Williams, Joseph D. (Box-folder 527: 7)
    - Wilson, David (Box-folder 527: 8)
    - Wolaner, Robin (Box-folder 527: 9)
  - 1990
    - General (Box-folder 527: 10)
    - Adedeji, Adebayo (Box-folder 527: 11)
    - Alameda Chapter restaurant series (Box-folder 527: 12)
    - Alexander, Michael (Box-folder 527: 13)
    - Ames, Bruce N. (Box-folder 527: 14)
    - Amory, Cleveland (Box-folder 527: 15)
    - Anderson, Martin (Box-folder 527: 16)
    - Andreotti, Giulio (Box-folder 527: 17)
    - Antall, Joseph (Box-folder 527: 18)
    - Arad, Moshe (Box-folder 527: 19)
    - Aramburu, Al (Box-folder 527: 20)
    - Asimov, Isaac (Box-folder 527: 21)
    - Bass, Barbara (Box-folder 527: 22)
    - Bechtel, Riley (Box-folder 527: 23)
    - Belafonte, Harry (Box-folder 527: 24)
    - Belsasso, Guido (Box-folder 527: 25)
    - Berkeley mayoral debate (Box-folder 527: 26)
    - "Big Green Initiative" (Box-folder 527: 27-28)
    - Bishop, J. Michael (Box-folder 527: 29)
    - Bleiberg, Robert M. (Box-folder 527: 30)
    - Bolt, Bruce (Box-folder 527: 31)
    - Bonner, Elena (Box-folder 528: 1)
    - Brady, James S. (Box-folder 528: 2)
    - Breeden, Richard (Box-folder 528: 3)
    - Brown, Edmund G. (Box-folder 528: 4)
    - Brown, Helen Gurley (Box-folder 528: 5)
    - Burleigh, Peter (Box-folder 528: 6)
    - Butcher, Susan (Box-folder 528: 7)
    - Butcher, Willard C. (Box-folder 528: 8)
    - Calderón Fournier, Rafael Angel (Box-folder 528: 9)
    - Callejas, Rafael Leonardo (Box-folder 528: 10)
    - Carl XVI Gustaf, King of Sweden (Box-folder 528: 11)
    - Carson, Johnny (Box-folder 528: 12)
    - Cartoon Art Museum (Box-folder 528: 13)
    - Chabot Science Center (Box-folder 528: 14)
    - Chao, Elaine (Box-folder 528: 15)
    - Cheng, Nien (Box-folder 528: 16)
    - Chisholm,, Shirley (Box-folder 528: 17)
    - Clark, William (Box-folder 528: 18)
    - Clinton, Bill (Box-folder 528: 19)
    - Cole, Johnetta B. (Box-folder 528: 20)
    - Craig, Gordon A. (Box-folder 528: 21)
    - Curran, John (Box-folder 528: 22)
    - Dal Bon, James J. (Box-folder 528: 23)
    - Dart, Justin (Box-folder 528: 24)
    - De Klerk, Frederik Willem (Box-folder 528: 25)
    - Dertouzos, Michael L. (Box-folder 528: 26)
    - Diof, Abdow (Box-folder 528: 27)
    - Douglas, Kirk (Box-folder 528: 28)
    - Downs, Hugh (Box-folder 528: 29)
    - Drucker, Peter F. (Box-folder 528: 30)
    - Drury, Allen (Box-folder 528: 31)
    - Dunn, Lydia (Box-folder 528: 32)
    - Durrett, Charles, and Kathryn McCamaut (Box-folder 528: 33)
    - Earle, Sylvia (Box-folder 529: 1)
    - Edwards, Harry (Box-folder 529: 2)
    - Eliasson, Jan (Box-folder 529: 3)
    - Enthoven, Alain (Box-folder 529: 4)
    - Esherich, Joe (Box-folder 529: 5)
    - Fallows, James M. (Box-folder 529: 6)
    - Feinstein, Dianne (Box-folder 529: 7)
    - Fighter pilots (Box-folder 529: 8)
    - Firstenberg, Jean Picker (Box-folder 529: 9)
    - Fischer, Michael (Box-folder 529: 10)
    - Fisher, Robert M. (Box-folder 529: 11)
    - Fleet Week (Box-folder 529: 12)
    - Fornos, Werner H. (Box-folder 529: 13)
    - Fountain, Pete (Box-folder 529: 14)
    - Frye, Northrop (Box-folder 529: 15)
    - Fuentes, Carlos (Box-folder 529: 16)
    - Fulghum, Robert (Box-folder 529: 17)
    - Gardner, Henry (Box-folder 529: 18)
    - Gardner, John (Box-folder 529: 19)
    - Gates, Bill (Box-folder 529: 20)
    - Gephardt, Richard A. (Box-folder 529: 21)
    - Gergen, David (Box-folder 529: 22)
    - Gleick, James (Box-folder 529: 23)
    - Goldstein, Ross (Box-folder 529: 24)
    - Goldwater, Barry (Box-folder 529: 25)
    - Góncz, Árpád (Box-folder 529: 26)
    - Gonzalez, Felipe (Box-folder 529: 27)
    - Gonzalez, Sam (Box-folder 529: 28)
    - Gottlieb, Robert (Box-folder 530: 1)
    - Green, Aaron and Al Arambura (Box-folder 530: 2)
    - Greenberg, Alan C. (Box-folder 530: 3)
    - Greenberg, Reuben (Box-folder 530: 4)
    - Greiff, Monica de (Box-folder 530: 5)
    - Groening, Matt (Box-folder 530: 6)
    - Grosvenor, Gilbert (Box-folder 530: 7)
    - Guibault, Rose (Box-folder 530: 8)
    - Hall, Arsenio (Box-folder 530: 9)
    - Han, Xu (Box-folder 530: 10)
    - Handy, Charles (Box-folder 530: 11)
    - Hanson, Dale (Box-folder 530: 12)
    - Harding, Harry (Box-folder 530: 13)
    - Hart, Jo-Anne (Box-folder 530: 14)
    - Hasi, Vencel (Box-folder 530: 15)
    - Hassan II, King of Morocco (Box-folder 530: 16)
    - Haughey, Charles (Box-folder 530: 17)
    - Hawke, Robert (Box-folder 530: 18)
    - Hay, Joel W. (Box-folder 530: 19)
    - Height, Dorothy (Box-folder 530: 20)
    - Herres, Robert T. (Box-folder 530: 21)
    - Herter, Frederic P. (Box-folder 530: 22)
    - Herzog, Chaim (Box-folder 530: 23)
    - Holiday concert (Box-folder 530: 24)
    - Holiday dinner (Box-folder 530: 25)
    - Honig, Bill (Box-folder 530: 26)
    - Hopman, Terry, and William Poole (Box-folder 530: 27)
    - Horner, Jack (Box-folder 530: 28)
    - Hume, John (Box-folder 531: 1)
    - Hunter-Gault, Charlayne (Box-folder 531: 2)
    - Hussain, Abid (Box-folder 531: 3)
    - Iacocca, Lee (Box-folder 531: 4)
    - Insurance commissioner debate (Box-folder 531: 5)
    - Jampolsky, Gerald G., and Diane V. Cirincione (Box-folder 531: 6)
    - Jenkins, Lord (Box-folder 531: 7)
    - Johan, James O. C. (Box-folder 531: 8)
    - Johnson, Moira (Box-folder 531: 9)
    - Jones, James Earl (Box-folder 531: 10)
    - Juan Carlos I, King of Spain (Box-folder 531: 11)
    - Kafitz, Chris (Box-folder 531: 12)
    - Kaifu, Toshiki (Box-folder 531: 13)
    - Kandemir, Nuzhet, and Semra Ozal (Box-folder 531: 14)
    - Karnow, Stanley A. (Box-folder 531: 15)
    - Kass, Leon Richard (Box-folder 531: 16)
    - Keker, John (Box-folder 531: 17)
    - Kemp, Jack (Box-folder 531: 18)
    - Kime, William (Box-folder 531: 19)
    - King, Don (Box-folder 531: 20)
    - King, Stephen (Box-folder 531: 21)
    - Kinnear, James W. (Box-folder 531: 22)
    - Kitzhaber, John (Box-folder 531: 23)
    - Klimova, Rita (Box-folder 531: 24)
    - Kney-Tal, Harry (Box-folder 531: 25)
    - Kohl, Helmut (Box-folder 532: 1)
    - Kuenheim, Eberhard von (Box-folder 532: 2)
    - Landor, Walter (Box-folder 532: 3)
    - Lane, John R. (Box-folder 532: 4)
    - Lantos, Tom (Box-folder 532: 5)
    - Larson, Charles R. (Box-folder 532: 6)
    - La Russa, Tony (Box-folder 532: 7)
    - Lawrence Livermore tour (Box-folder 532: 8)
    - Lawson, Fred H. (Box-folder 532: 9)
    - Lilienthal, Sally (Box-folder 532: 10)
    - Ling, Chai (Box-folder 532: 11)
    - Lipset, Seymour (Box-folder 532: 12)
    - Liquor Tax Initiative (Andrew McGuire and Richard Mauter) (Box-folder 532: 13)
    - Lord, Bette Bao (Box-folder 532: 14)
    - Lorenzo, Frank (Box-folder 532: 15)
    - McCarthy, Eugene (Box-folder 532: 16)
    - McClintock, Jessica (Box-folder 532: 17)
    - Major, John (Box-folder 532: 18)
    - Mandela, Nelson (Box-folder 532: 19)
    - Mansour, Riyad (Box-folder 532: 20)
    - Maran, Stephen P. (Box-folder 532: 21)
    - Marin restaurant series (Box-folder 532: 22)
    - Al-Mashat, Mohamed Sadiq (Box-folder 532: 23)
    - Mathews, Jessica Tuchman (Box-folder 532: 24)
    - Matveyev, Alexander (Box-folder 532: 25)
    - Maude, Francis (Box-folder 532: 26)
    - May, Rollo (Box-folder 532: 27)
    - Mesa, Pete (Box-folder 532: 28)
    - Mirassou dinner (Box-folder 532: 29)
    - Mitchell, Bobby (Box-folder 532: 30)
    - Moiseyev, Mikhail (Box-folder 532: 31)
    - Monagan, Robert (Box-folder 533: 1)
    - Montana, Joe (Box-folder 533: 2)
    - Morgan, Michael (Box-folder 533: 3)
    - Morgan, Rebecca (Box-folder 533: 4)
    - Myers, Norman (Box-folder 533: 5)
    - Naber, John (Box-folder 533: 6)
    - Neal, Eric (Box-folder 533: 7)
    - Newsweek panel of editors (Box-folder 533: 8)
    - Oakland mayoral debate (Box-folder 533: 9)
    - Ogden, Chris (Box-folder 533: 10)
    - Pauley, Jane (Box-folder 533: 11)
    - Pauling, Linus (Box-folder 533: 12)
    - Pell, Eugene (Box-folder 533: 13)
    - Perata, Don (Box-folder 533: 14)
    - Perella, Joseph R. (Box-folder 533: 15)
    - Peters, Tom (with Toni Casey and Larry Stone) (Box-folder 533: 16)
    - Petkov, Krustyo I. (Box-folder 533: 17)
    - Pickering, Thomas R. (Box-folder 533: 18)
    - Pollack, Sydney (Box-folder 533: 19)
    - Porter, Roger (Box-folder 533: 20)
    - Post, Rollin (Box-folder 533: 21)
    - Richards, Ann (Box-folder 533: 22)
    - Ris, Howard (Box-folder 533: 23)
    - Rosenberg, Alan I. (Box-folder 533: 24)
    - Rosenthal, James O. (Box-folder 533: 25)
    - Ross, Ian M. (Box-folder 533: 26)
    - Rowell, Galen (Box-folder 533: 27)
    - Safire, William (Box-folder 533: 28)
    - Sakai, Kuniyasu (Box-folder 533: 29)
    - San Jose mayoral debate (Box-folder 533: 30)
    - Sasson, Mosha (Box-folder 534: 1)
    - Schwarte, Buz (Box-folder 534: 2)
    - Schwarzenegger, Arnold (Box-folder 534: 3)
    - Sharpe, William (Box-folder 534: 4)
    - Sharansky, Natan (Box-folder 534: 5)
    - Sheehan, James (Box-folder 534: 6)
    - Sherifis, Michael E. (Box-folder 534: 7)
    - Shirer, William (Box-folder 534: 8)
    - Siracusa, Angelo (Box-folder 534: 9)
    - Smiler, Helen (Box-folder 534: 11)
    - Soeharto (Box-folder 534: 12)
    - Solomon, Ezra Lee (Box-folder 534: 13)
    - Starr, Marvin B. (Box-folder 534: 14)
    - Steinberg, Leigh (Box-folder 534: 15)
    - Stone, Michael P. W. (Box-folder 534: 16)
    - Sullivan, Louis W. (Box-folder 534: 17)
    - Taylor, Elizabeth (Box-folder 534: 18)
    - Thatcher, Margaret (Box-folder 534: 19)
    - Thomas, Franklin (Box-folder 534: 20)
    - Thurow, Lester C. (Box-folder 534: 21)
    - Turow, Scott (Box-folder 534: 22)
    - Venkataraman, Ramaswami (Box-folder 534: 23)
    - Waldheim, Kurt (Box-folder 534: 24)
    - Walters, Barbara (Box-folder 534: 25)
    - Watson, Thomas J. (Box-folder 534: 26)
    - Wattenberg, Ben J. (Box-folder 534: 27)
    - Wellman, Mark (Box-folder 534: 28)
    - Wilbur, Richard (Box-folder 534: 29)
    - Yalom, Iru (Box-folder 534: 30)
    - Zamora, James Paz (Box-folder 534: 31)
  - 1991
    - General (Box-folder 534: 32)
    - Abboud, Farid (Box-folder 534: 33)
    - Abrahamson, James A. (Box-folder 534: 34)
    - Acapulco Restaurant "A Moveable Feast" (Box-folder 534: 35)
    - Adams-Ender, Clara (Box-folder 534: 36)
    - Alberthal, Les (Box-folder 534: 37)
    - Arbesa, Jose (Box-folder 534: 38)
    - Armstrong, Anne L. (Box-folder 534: 39)
    - Arnold, Richard K., and Tom Tyrrell (Box-folder 534: 40)
    - Aronoff, Ben (Box-folder 534: 41)
    - Attles, Al (Box-folder 534: 42)
    - Baker, James K. (Box-folder 534: 43)
    - Bay Meadows (Box-folder 535: 1)
    - Bergsten, Fred C. (Box-folder 535: 2)
    - Berning, Jonne (Box-folder 535: 3)
    - Berry, Joyce (Box-folder 535: 4)
    - Bocharov, Michael (Box-folder 535: 5)
    - Bolaffi, Guilio (Box-folder 535: 6)
    - Brady, Nicolas F. (Box-folder 535: 7)
    - Brazelton, Berry (Box-folder 535: 8)
    - Bricklin, Mark (Box-folder 535: 9)
    - Brock, William E. (Box-folder 535: 10)
    - Brown, Eddie F. (Box-folder 535: 11)
    - Brown, Iona (Box-folder 535: 12)
    - Brown, Julia (Box-folder 535: 13)
    - Brown, Ron (Box-folder 535: 14)
    - Brown, Stephen (Box-folder 535: 15)
    - Brundland, Gro Harlem (Box-folder 535: 16)
    - Bunzel, John H. (Box-folder 535: 17)
    - Burke, Yvonne Braithwaite (Box-folder 535: 18)
    - Burt, Richard R. (Box-folder 535: 19)
    - Caldicott, Helen (Box-folder 535: 20)
    - California Shakespeare Festival (Box-folder 535: 21)
    - Campbell, Tom (Box-folder 535: 22)
    - Casey, Donald M. (Box-folder 536: 1)
    - Castrey, Bonnie (Box-folder 536: 2)
    - Charchalia, George, and Ernest Briskey (Box-folder 536: 3)
    - Charles, Ray, and Etta James (Box-folder 536: 4)
    - Chavez, Linda (Box-folder 536: 5)
    - Clinton, Bill (Box-folder 536: 6)
    - Cogan, John (Box-folder 536: 7)
    - Commanday, Robert (Box-folder 536: 8)
    - Conley, Frances F. (Box-folder 536: 9)
    - Cornell University (Box-folder 536: 10)
    - Cousteau, Jacques-Yves (Box-folder 536: 11)
    - Cronk, Rick (Box-folder 536: 12)
    - Curien, Gilles (Box-folder 536: 13)
    - Cutler, Walter L. (Box-folder 536: 14)
    - Denver, John (Box-folder 536: 15)
    - Designer showhouse (Box-folder 536: 16)
    - Diamond, Marion Cleeves (Box-folder 536: 17)
    - Ding, Mou-shi (Box-folder 536: 18)
    - Dixon, Sharon Pratt (Box-folder 536: 19)
    - Djerassi, Carl (Box-folder 536: 20)
    - Doder, Dusko (Box-folder 536: 21)
    - Donaldson, William (Box-folder 537: 1)
    - Dowling, Patrick (Box-folder 537: 2)
    - Driewanowski, Kazimierz (Box-folder 537: 3)
    - Driscoll, Jerry (Box-folder 537: 4)
    - Drought panel (Box-folder 537: 5)
    - Edell, Dean (Box-folder 537: 6)
    - Emergency preparedness panel (Box-folder 537: 7)
    - Environmental panel (Box-folder 537: 8-9)
    - Erdman, Paul (Box-folder 537: 10-11)
    - Evanhoe, Michael, and William Kempton (Box-folder 537: 12)
    - Fang, Li-zhi (Box-folder 537: 13)
    - Fleet Week (Box-folder 537: 14)
    - Flesch, Colette (Box-folder 537: 15)
    - Fraknoi, Andrew (Box-folder 537: 16-17)
    - Fujimori, Alberto (Box-folder 537: 18)
    - Garcia, Pedro Sordo (Box-folder 537: 19)
    - Gavin, John (Box-folder 537: 20)
    - Gazit, Shlomo (Box-folder 537: 21)
    - Gingerbread House dinner (Box-folder 537: 22)
    - Global strategies panel (Box-folder 537: 23)
    - Gold, Herbert (Box-folder 537: 24)
    - Goldberg, Fred T. (Box-folder 537: 25)
    - Goldstein, Sydney (Box-folder 537: 26)
    - Guiton, Bommie (Box-folder 538: 1)
    - Gumbel, Bryant (Box-folder 538: 2)
    - Gutierrez, Asuncion (Box-folder 538: 3)
    - Gutleben, Robert (Box-folder 538: 4)
    - Hammami, Hussein (Box-folder 538: 5)
    - Hansen, Bev, and Janet Nicholas (Box-folder 538: 6)
    - Hardesty, Nancy, and Joyce Leonard (Box-folder 538: 7)
    - Hardiman, Joseph (Box-folder 538: 8)
    - Hatcher, Patrick (Box-folder 538: 9)
    - Henderson, Katherine Usher (Box-folder 538: 10)
    - Hewson, John (Box-folder 538: 11)
    - Hill, Anita (Box-folder 538: 12)
    - Holiday, J. S. (Box-folder 538: 13)
    - Holiday concert (Box-folder 538: 14)
    - Holiday sing-along - Masterworks Chorale (Box-folder 538: 15)
    - Hutchison, Claude B. (Box-folder 538: 16)
    - Indyk, Martin, and Elie Kedourie (Box-folder 538: 17)
    - International economics panel (Box-folder 538: 18)
    - Jampolsky, Gerald, and Diane V. Cirincone (Box-folder 538: 19)
    - Jordan, Vernon (Box-folder 538: 20)
    - Josephson, Michael (Box-folder 538: 21)
    - Kahn, Alfred E. (Box-folder 538: 22)
    - Keller, George (Box-folder 538: 23)
    - Kennedy, David (Box-folder 538: 24)
    - Kennedy, Donald (Box-folder 538: 25)
    - Kersting, Cassandra (Box-folder 538: 26)
    - Kessler, David (Box-folder 538: 27)
    - King, Coretta Scott (Box-folder 538: 28)
    - Kingsley, Bostsweletse (Box-folder 538: 29)
    - Kingston, Maxine Hong (Box-folder 538: 30)
    - Koppel, Ted (Box-folder 538: 31)
    - Kozol, Jonathan (Box-folder 538: 32)
    - Kraft, Robert P. (Box-folder 539: 1)
    - Krevans, Julius (Box-folder 539: 2)
    - Kurtzig, Sandra (Box-folder 539: 3)
    - Lamm, Richard (Box-folder 539: 4)
    - Lane, Mel, and Scott Wiley (Box-folder 539: 5)
    - Lang, Howard (Box-folder 539: 6-7)
    - Lee, Martin (Box-folder 539: 8)
    - Liechtenstein, Alfred von (Box-folder 539: 9)
    - Lightfoot, Sara Lawrence (Box-folder 539: 10)
    - Link, William P. (Box-folder 539: 11)
    - Lipson, Leslie (Box-folder 539: 12)
    - Lujan, Manuel (Box-folder 539: 13)
    - Lynch, David (Box-folder 539: 14)
    - McCloskey, Paul N. (Box-folder 539: 15)
    - MacLeish, Roderick (Box-folder 539: 16)
    - Maibach, Michael, and George Brown (Box-folder 539: 17)
    - Mailer, Norman (Box-folder 539: 18)
    - Maksoud, Clovis (Box-folder 539: 19)
    - Malpass, David (Box-folder 539: 20)
    - Marshall, Colin (Box-folder 539: 21)
    - Masur, Kurt (Box-folder 539: 22)
    - Maytag, Fritz (Box-folder 539: 23)
    - Middlebrook, Diane (Box-folder 539: 24)
    - Miller, Debbie (Box-folder 539: 25)
    - "Les Misérables" (evening at) (Box-folder 539: 26)
    - Moore, Dale (Box-folder 539: 27)
    - Morris, Stanley (Box-folder 539: 28)